# Akhmadjon Abdusamadov

Software Engineer



https://www.linkedin.com/in/akhmadjonabdusamdov/info.ahmadjon@gmail.com+998-97-129-9777ahmadjon.uzt.me/AkhmadjonAbdusamadov

# About Me

I've been coding over 5 years. I am a software developer who loves building full-stack applications & learning new technologies. I've also helped a number of people learn how to code.

My interests in programming lead me to study Computer Science deeper. I have learned different types of programming languages in my university. Learning new languages is so much enjoyable as they open new solutions to actual problems and make people's lives easier.

# Work Experience (5 years)



**Web developer,** Freelancing remotely Working on different fixed-time projects as a freelancer. *Jul 2023 to present* 

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Vue.js, Next.js

# Responsibilities:

- Meeting with the client to discuss technical analysis.
- Reviewing design and requirements and giving estimations for the fixed TA.
- Reviewing current applications if it's already there and getting used to project traditions.
- Updating clients constantly about the progress with calls or texts.
- Enhanced knowledge and experience by learning new skills.
- Delivered high-quality results on time by given estimations.
- Developing and implementing highly responsive user interface components using the next, react or vue concepts.



React Software Engineer, at Codemotion Ninjas LLC

Codemotion Ninjas LLC provides complex web and mobile development for Fintech, Logistics and Startups. *May 2022 to Jul 2023* 

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Vue.js, Next.js

### Responsibilities:

- Meeting with the development team to discuss user interface ideas and applications.
- Reviewing application requirements and interface designs.
- · Identifying web-based user interactions.
- Developing and implementing highly responsive user interface components using react concepts.



### **Software Engineer**, at EPAM System

EPAM System is a global job platform offering remote work opportunities for tech professionals. 2021 - 2022 (full-time)

Stack: React, React context API, Typescript

#### Mentor:

- · Mentoring new comers in lab
- · Being technical interviewer

### Responsibilities:

- · Developed the logic of the front Integrations
- Fixed bugs
- · Wrote tests
- Developed a UI Components
- · Optimized performance

# Project metrics and key features:

- 10000+ simultaneous users
- 2 TB of CDN data
- 1000+ marketing campaigns launched Transactions queue allowing third-party downtime



### Full stack developer, at Alitech Website Solutions

Alitech Website Solutions 2019 - 2021 (full-time)

Stack: React, Redux-toolkit, thunk, Nodejs, ExpressJs, MongoDB

### Responsibilities:

- Developed the logic of the application
- Designed UI elements
- Created API
- Implemented real-time tracking
- Participated in integration with 3rd party systems (leaflet map and etc) Integration with DB
- Fixed bugs
- Organized and managed operational troubleshooting and performance optimization processes of application



# Frontend Developer, at Alitech Website Solutions

Alitech Website Solutions 2018 - 2019 (full-time)

**Stack**: Typescript, React, Redux,

# Responsibilities:

- Developed the logic of the front
- Wrote tests
- · Fixed bugs
- Implemented authorization for different countries/roles Developed autopay steps
- Developed a UI Components

# Project metrics and key features:

• 20000+ simultaneous users Real-Time photo-based KYC

# Hard Skills

- HTML & CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, JavaScript (ES6...), Typescript, jQuery, Redux, Material UI. Antd
- React, Vue, Next.
- Jest, Enzyme
- Node.js, Express, REST API, Socket.io, WebPack, GraphQL,
- MongoDB,SQL,
- Firebase
- React Native
- Figma, Command Line,

# **Education History**

### Radio devices and networks

Institution: Jizzakh Polytechnic institute Year of Graduation: 2022

- GPA 5
- Mentor Frontend Dev Club
- First Place at Newldea Hackathon among universities

# Alicode academy

Web development 2017 - 2018

# LinkedIn licenses & certifications

- Create a CRM Mobile Application with React Native
- JavaScript: Best Practices for Functions and Classes
- Node.js: Microservices

# Volunteer Work and Affiliations

### Mentor

The IT Park of Jizzakh city 2020 to 2021

Every month, I volunteer to teach frontend literacy to children

# Soft Skills

- Ability to analyze complex technical data
- Analyze and create database structures
- The desire to solve logical problems quickly, to master technology quickly, regularly

# Language

- Uzbek (Native)
- English advanced
- Russian elementary